Christian Franco

Nationality: Spanish Date of birth: 09/06/2001 Phone number: (+34) 626554625

■ Email address: christianfrancosoto@gmail.com

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/christian-franco-soto/

Website: christianfranco.dev

• Home: (Spain)

ABOUT ME

I'm a full-stack developer with a strong focus on back-end and solid knowledge in web development, with 3 years of experience in software development. My passion for programming is combined with a desire to learn and improve my knowledge.

WORK EXPERIENCE

III *Inorca* – Spain

Country: Spain

Full Stack Developer

[08/2023 - Current]

Application and REST API development using .Net Core (C#) for the backend and Angular (TypeScript) for the frontend, using SQL Server and PostgreSQL for database management.

I have also contributed in a web application working on the frontend and functionality with React and .Net Core. I have used other tools like Git (GitLab) or Postman.

Ⅲ Técnicas Competitivas S.A. – Spain

Country: Spain

Junior Software Developer

[06/2022 - 08/2023]

- Development and maintenance of a web application for economic management using C# ASP.NET MVC.
- Development, management and maintenance of a database in SQL Server.
- Working group with Scrum methodology.
- Version control with GitLab.
- Use of other tools: NUnit for testing, SonarQube for code quality, DocFX to generate documentation and Jenkins for continuous integration.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Higher Technician in Multi-platform Applications Development

CIFP César Manrique [09/2020 – 06/2022]

Country: Spain

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Spanish
Other language(s): English

SKILLS